Do Le Long An

dolelongan@gmail.com | 0937022184 | SkyGarden 3, Phu My Hung Residential Area, District 7

ABOUT ME

Having previously majored in Computer Science and Data Science at UWA, I am now studying at RMIT University in Vietnam, majoring in Information Technology. Due to my experience leading most of my projects, I developed the soft skills of Time Management and Leadership.

EDUCATION

Foundation Program - Advanced

Taylor's College Graduated with *GPA 3.0/4.0* 10/2019 - 06/2020

B.Sc. in Computer Science and Data Science

University of Western Australia 07/2020 - 12/2021

B.IT. in Web Development

RMIT University Vietnam *GPA 3.4/4.0* 06/2022 - Current

LINKS

あ LaansDole

in do-le-long-an

laansdole

HONORS & AWARDS

10/2019 - Taylors College Foundation Program Highest Scholarship -7,500AUD.

06/2020 - Australia's Global Excellence Scholarship - 15,000AUD per anum.

2021 - Best Regional Marketing Member in AIESEC Australia 2021.2.

VOLUNTEER

12/2019 - 03/2020 - StudyPerth Airport Greeter

 Guide and assist foreign students and guests at Perth Airport, Western Australia

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

RBLOG - Front End Developer

RMIT Vietnam - Building IT System - COSC2634

- Tech Stack used: MEN (MongoDB + Express + React + Node.js)
- · CSS Framework: Tailwind
- Objective: Giving the blogging community a platform that is easy to use.
- · Link to Website Demo: rmit-blog

E-Commerce Website - Project Leader

04/2023 - 05/2023

10/2022 - 01/2023

RMIT Vietnam - Web Programming - COSC2430

- Tech Stack used: MEN (MongoDB + Express + EJS + Node.js)
- CSS Framework: Bootstrap
- Objective: Our intention is to create an e-commerce website that draws inspiration from Lazada but simplifies the user interface and functionality.
- · Link to Web App Demo: group9-eCommerce
- · Link to Project GitHub repository: group9-eCommerce

Resume Builder

31/05/2023

- · Language used: LaTeX
- · Objective: Creating my own resume
- · Link to GitHub repository

SKILLS

AWS Academy Graduate - AWS Academy Cloud Foundations

03/2023 - 30/05/2023

RMIT Vietnam - Cloud Foundation - COSC2766

- Completion of AWS Cloud Practitioner Preparation.
- · Link to Cloud Foundation Badge

Data Structure and Algorithm

03/2023 - 30/05/2023

RMIT Vietnam - Data Structure and Algorithm - COSC2658

- · Language used: Java
- Problem-solving paradigms such as divide and conquer, decrease and conquer, greedy, and dynamic programming.
- · Link to Group Project repository

Others

06/2022 - Current

RMIT Vietnam - Software Engineering Design - EEET2482

· C++ Group Project

CO-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Micro: bit Automatic Plant Watering

07/2022 - 09/2022

RMIT Vietnam - NCT Club

Participating in developing Micro:bit Automatic Plant Watering

NCT Landing Page

11/2022 - 03/2023

RMIT Vietnam - NCT Club

Participating in developing NCT Landing page

RMIT Business Plan Competition

05/2023 - Current

RMIT Vietnam - FinTect Club

Participating in developing Event Landing Page

Last updated May 31, 2023